Now, I know the commitment to misunderstanding me is one that many of you all have taken a vow of.
Nonetheless, I come here to further explain my messaging.
When I say that this is Black people's fight, I say that understanding that there is a multi-pronged approach to resistance.
It's like, look at the Smart, Funny, and Black logo.
Rebel Fam, Woke Fam, Culture Fam, Fly Fam, the fighters, the thinkers, the artists, the innovators.
I do not believe Black people should be on the front lines right now.
By no means.
Listen to this priest right here.
I have told the clergy of the Episcopal Diocese of New Hampshire, make sure they have their wills written.
Because it may be that now is no longer the time for statements, but for us with our bodies to stand between the powers of this world and the most vulnerable.
When I hear Black people say, this is none of my business, this isn't my fight, you ain't never fought for nothing before.
Because you would know if you have fought that there are so many places to be in the fight beyond the front line.
There are so many necessary roles in support beyond being on the front line.
And when I said your Blackness is flimsy, what I'm referring to is the fact that you don't realize the depth of your own Blackness and its ability to show up beyond simply being a body.
Because you are still looking at yourself the same way a colonizer looks at you.
As simply a body with Black skin.
No, baby, you are more than that.
And when you are grounded in this, you understand that you have an uncanny ability to innovate.
You understand that you have an uncanny connection to spiritual power.
You understand you have an uncanny connection to seasoning your food.
And what does the movement need?
The movement needs spirituality.
The movement needs artistry and innovation.
And the movement needs sustenance.
There will absolutely be no effort of protection happening in your silo.
None.
White people, you're on the front line.
Everybody else, we got other work to do.
That's a very easy message that anyone can get behind.
And if you still mad, it's because you want to be.
Smart, funny, it!
Smart!